at-la.com 2016-10-20

# @LA Privacy Policy

|  |   
`** Our Privacy Policy   
**`  
---|---|---  
|  |  |  |    
---|---  
|    
---  
|  About @LA  
|  Access Statistics  
|  Advertising in @LA  
|  Awards / @LA in the Media  
|  Feedback from @LA's Users  
|  Member Site Information  
|  News / Recent Developments  
| 

Introduction  
Information Collection and Use  
Information Sharing Disclosure  
Use of Cookies  
Confidentiality and Security  
Changes to our Privacy Policy  

Index |  `**Introduction**`  
|  |  We at @LA take your privacy and the security of the personal information we collect about you very seriously. 

@LA is owned by Technique Development and this privacy policy applies to all websites owned by Technique Development.   

Index |  `**Information Collection and Use**`  
|  |  @LA does not collect personal information when you navigate our site. 

@LA may require information when you purchase products through our site. 

In the future, @LA may offer features that require you to register in order to use them. At this time, we will ask for information such as your name, email address, address, birth date and other personal information. register with Yahoo!, when you use Yahoo! products or services, when you visit Yahoo! pages or the pages of certain Yahoo! partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Yahoo! may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with Yahoo! and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

@LA collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 

@LA automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. 

@LA uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

@LA does not target advertising based on personal information or provide such information to our advertisers.   

Index |  `**Information Sharing Disclosure**`  
|  |  @LA does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

@LA may provide your information to trusted partners who work with @LA under confidentiality agreements which prevent them from independently using or sharing the information. 

In the case of legal actions or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, @LA may be compelled or volunteer to supply any personal information we have collected. 

Should @LA believe it necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of @LA's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, we would supply such information to any law enforcement agency or other parties to the investigation.   

Index |  `**Use of Cookies**`  
|  |  @LA does not currently use cookies. 

At such time that @LA does use cookies, they will only be used to aid in the navigation, security, personalization and convenience of using our site. We do not use cookies to market products or services to you. No personal identifying information will be stored in a cookie. 

If your computer does not accept the use of cookies, then any advanced features that we provide will be disabled. 

@LA lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to @LA's cookies.   

Index |  `**Confidentiality and Security**`  
|  |  Your @LA Account Information is password-protected. We will not release your password to anyone except through our secure automated password recovery system. 

@LA limits access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

@LA implements various and numerous physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards to prevent illegal and unauthorized access to your personal information, and make our best efforts at maintaining such security, however @LA cannot guarantee with 100% certainty that a security breach will not occur.   

Index |  `**Changes to our Privacy Policy**`  
|  |  @LA may update our privacy policy. If we make significant changes regarding how your personal information is handled we will place a prominent notice on our home page for 30 days after the change. If you have an account with us, a notice will placed on the initial login page for 30 days after the change.   

|  |  __All text, images and HTML © 1995-2012[Technique Development](http://www.techdev.com/). All Rights Reserved. @LA is a registered trademark of Technique Development. The information on this page is presented as is. No warranty as to the accuracy of any of the presented information is implied. For questions/comments/feedback, send email to [webmaster@at-la.com](mailto:webmaster@at-la.com).  
This page is located at <http://www.at-la.com/@la-info/privacy.htm>. __
